Did you hear ?
Is that our land ?
No , it 's in the forest .
Maybe Ruiz ?
Or some poacher ?
No , a poacher doesn 't shoot so much .
- Should we take the dogs ? - No , they 'll see us .
I counted three .
Then it stopped . And two more .
They are not hunting .
It 's not a rifle .
It 's a revolver .
Get a coat .
Was it here or at Ruiz 's ?
It was near .
We 'll leave at dawn .
WHEN EVIL LURKS
Shit .
A puma ?
There was a big one stalking around .
It ate Ruiz 's goats .
Isn 't this Ruiz ?
He was hunting the puma .
He lost to the cat .
No .
This guy was cut with something sharp .
What do we do ?
We have to report it .
These are pieces of something .
I 've seen this somewhere .
What is it for ?
I don 't know , brother .
We are at Ruiz 's now .
We have to tell him .
Or the police ?
What if the killer is Ruiz ?
He caught him stealing and killed him .
Ruiz wouldn 't cut someone in half , shut up .
He cuts him up , making him disappear ,
feeding him to the pigs ... - What happened with Ruiz ?
Why ?
Did something happen with Ruiz that you are not telling me ?
He doesn 't like us .
He doesn 't like you !
He was going ...
or coming .
He was taking a shortcut to the hill .
To Maria Elena 's house .
Was he a relative ?
What 's this language ?
I 've seen this .
- Russian maybe ? - Russian ?
Look , Maria Elena Gomez .
What 's going on with these dogs ?
Hi , Maria Elena .
How are you ?
Long time no see .
We are here
about last night 's gun shots , did you hear them ?
We looked around with Jimmy and the dogs ,
nearby .
We found someone you may know .
Were you waiting for someone ?
Because he ...
he won 't make it .
He had a problem .
When will he arrive ?
He must have arrived long ago .
We are waiting for him .
For him to deal with my son .
Uriel ?
Yes .
He has to kill my son .
He has to kill Uriel .
He is possessed ,
he 's been rotten for a long time .
We were waiting for them to dispose of him .
It 's my fault .
I thought that by praying
we would be able to heal him .
We lit a candle to the Saint -
Churches are dead , ma 'am .
Dead .
We were afraid of speaking .
Afraid of getting kicked off the land by Ruiz and the neighbors .
We have nothing .
We have no place to go .
We thought we could heal him .
We took care of him so he didn 't die .
So they can kill him .
But it 's taking too long .
Have you reported this ?
A year ago , or more .
A year ?
Who did you tell ?
The lady 's son ?
Yes , the older one .
She didn 't speak to me . And to you , Superintendent ?
Did you see him ?
Well .
What did you see ?
Tell me .
Have you ever seen a rotten before ?
So ?
How do you know ?
As they say , Gutierrez ,
when you see one , you know it .
And we knew it , easy .
You are under the influence .
Many cases of possessed ones are fake .
And we are here , in the middle of nowhere -
Uriel is dying !
He is swollen , he is a ball of pus .
Bring the Mayor .
Give me the phone .
Call him .
Give me the number , I 'll do it , no problem .
He must face this .
Nobody tells me what to do .
Especially you , Yazurlo .
Especially you .
It took a year .
A whole year passed and you only sent the cleaner yesterday .
Don 't raise your voice .
Nobody spoke to me about this .
You 'll have a hard time , again .
You don 't believe me , do you ?
Leave him .
Give me an excuse to lock you up .
You won 't get out easily , lunatic .
Easy , brother .
We found the cleaner dead .
We found him in pieces , don 't you get it ?
There 's a protocol for cases like this .
We call , Public Health comes and they solve it .
Done .
That 's what we 'll do .
Do as you like .
Why was the cleaner killed ?
Who ?
Ruiz killed him ?
Ruiz ?
I doubt everything .
We are at the end of the world .
Why would there be a possessed one here ?
What are you saying ?
They won 't come and see the body .
Not even the rotten , they told me .
They said it 's not their problem .
They washed their hands .
But someone killed him , Ruiz .
Someone trying to prevent the cleaner
from reaching Maria 's place .
And the Mayor ?
They called him .
He knew , a year ago .
He just let it pass .
He said he thought it was already solved .
They asked us not to speak ,
or we 'll be marked and this place will be worthless .
A ghost town , Ruiz .
We lose everything .
They suggested we leave until they send a new cleaner from ...
the Ministry .
When ?
They didn 't say .
There 's no time , Uriel is about to die ,
we can 't wait for a cleaner .
Leave ,
close our mouths
and leave .
We 'll have to arm ourselves .
Arm ourselves ?
Against what ?
My dogs left a month ago .
The four of them .
First they make the animals go crazy , they say .
Then they even make the deceased crazy .
What shall we do ?
Something , we have to do something .
Maybe we have to auction everything off .
Leave before this goes viral .
The naive brothers .
This was a set up .
It was the State .
They want my land .
That 's why they abandon us , they don 't care about us .
A possessed one here .
I never imagined this .
Armando , where are you going ?
Don 't do something stupid .
Holy Mary !
Mr. Ruiz .
God , what are you doing ?
What are you doing ?
Motherfuckers ...
No ,
look what they brought .
They brought the foulest thing to my land .
Don 't shoot .
Mr. Ruiz , don 't shoot , please .
I have to do it .
You don 't kill evil like that , it will be worse .
If you kill him , you die .
It will take our bodies , it will take our souls .
Don 't do it , please , it will make it worse .
Worse .
It has to be done by a professional .
Shut up , fucker .
I should have burned your house down
when you came here , with your filth .
You contaminate everything .
Everything .
Motherfuckers .
Kill me , Ruiz .
Please ,
you coward , kill me .
Before I move to Jimena 's belly ,
and posses the life growing inside of her .
You 'll be the first I will visit
when I 'm released .
Armando .
What have you done ? Tell me you didn 't hurt anybody .
He 's playing , that 's all .
He can do what he wants , He plays with us .
Open the window .
He taunts us .
Armando .
He is alive , he didn 't do it .
You have to leave .
We are thinking about leaving .
Fuck everything , Ruiz .
No , he has to go .
We have to take him away .
Two or three hours from here . As far as we can .
- It 's too risky . - Risky is having him here .
- We don 't know how to do it . - Cowards .
I 'll do it with you ,
or I 'll do it myself .
This is my land .
The rotten must be removed before it rots the rest .
You have a family , Pedro .
Don 't you ?
Do it for them .
Take the risk .
What are you doing ?
Mr. Ruiz .
Don 't harm him .
What are you doing ? Don 't harm him .
He 's too big , he won 't pass .
I 'm not touching him .
Bring a rope , we tie his feet and drag him like a pig .
What are you doing ?
Taking him away .
Take him away ? Where ?
They are taking your brother .
Go grab a rope or a strap to tie him .
A rope ? Let 's lift him using the sheets .
Grab the sheets .
- They will break . - They won 't .
He is right , hold his feet and let 's lift him .
At the same time .
Together .
One , two , three , now .
Come on , together .
Harder , harder .
Wait , look .
Look !
Nasty fucker .
You are killing him .
Get out , you brat , or I 'll kill you .
Grab it , pull .
Here , pull .
Come on , come on , pull .
It 's stuck .
It 's full of shit .
Don 't touch him !
Let 's pull together .
Grab it .
Be careful with the steps .
Careful .
Pull , shit .
There , at the same time .
Together .
I 'm tired , he 's falling .
Harder , hold it there .
He 's falling .
Grab it , fuck you !
We need a blanket .
Go fetch a blanket .
Hurry up , asshole .
One , two , three .
Shall we throw him here or farther ?
How far are we ?
Three hundred kilometers .
Let 's go farther ,
a hundred more maybe .
Let 's check him and drive another hundred .
What a smell , damn it .
- Did you touch him ? - No , no .
We have to burn the clothes .
We did alright .
You did well .
This was the right thing to do .
Careful . Careful !
Damn .
Did you hit him ? - No , I didn 't
where did the brat come from ?
The asshole was going to school .
Asshole !
Motherfucker , just what we needed .
So dangerous .
God damn it !
Shall we drop him here ?
Yes .
And if he drowns ?
It 's kind of dry .
Damn it !
What happened ?
Did he jump ?
He can 't move .
No , it happened when we swerved ,
when he almost hit the kid .
I asked you to watch him , Jimmy .
I didn 't see it .
How did you not see that ?
I didn 't .
I saw that we almost killed a kid .
How long since the kid ?
Twenty minutes .
- Sure ? - More or less .
It 's back there .
Shall we load him again ?
It 's over .
It is far enough .
It 's not our fucking problem .
Armando .
That goat .
You .
No .
Leave , motherfucker .
Armando .
Don 't do it , wait .
Don 't shoot the beast with a firearm .
You 'll condemn us , love .
We will be parents , don 't do it , please .
Get out !
Leave , fucker .
Leave .
I went to Ruiz 's .
He was dead .
And his wife , too .
My mother disappeared .
What do you mean ? Where is she ?
Something happened ,
you did the wrong thing by taking Uriel away .
Did you see Ruiz dead ?
Let me stay here , I don 't want to go back alone .
You can 't stay , leave .
Please , I 'm freezing to death .
Please , Mr. Yazurlo .
Stay in the saddle room ,
you 'll find something to stay warm .
I don 't want him to stay .
You leave at dawn .
He is armed , you know that ?
Are you armed ?
Yes , Sir , I have a .38 .
Give it to him .
You leave as soon as the sun comes out .
You never come back .
Yes , Sir .
I must tell you something .
Don 't use electric lights .
Its shadows call in the evil .
Why did you let him stay ?
- He is scared , Jimmy . - Don 't say .
Do you believe him ?
His mother won 't abandon him .
Why would she ?
He is lying .
Five .
We won 't take anything from the house .
Valuables ?
No .
Nothing that was here ,
in this place .
No clothes ,
no memories .
We go to town ,
I pick up my kids ,
and we get out of here .
Open up .
It 's me , Pedro , we have to talk .
What 's going on , Pedro ?
We have to talk , let me in .
Does Sabrina know ? She hasn 't said anything .
I need to talk , let me in .
Wait .
You can 't enter .
Wait what ?
Come on , let me into my house .
What are you doing ?
Wake up Sabrina and the kids , too .
Bring two changes of clothes , for me and my brother ,
I 'll explain .
What are you doing ? What the fuck ?
Listen ,
if you are in trouble don 't involve my family .
Bring the clothes , it 's for everyone 's sake .
Bring them , hurry .
What the fuck ?
Sabrina , we need to talk .
Is he drunk ?
I don 't know , you can see for yourself .
Why are you doing naked ?
Leave immediately .
We need to talk .
Why are you in my house ?
Leave .
What 's this ?
We need to talk , things are happening .
You are insane .
There will be a disaster .
You can 't be here , leave immediately .
Do you hear me ?
Leave !
I need clothes .
Fuck .
Alcohol ?
Give me that .
- Don 't look at me like that . - You are insane .
I 'll explain .
Let 's go inside .
No , you are not coming in .
You 're violating the restraining order , are you aware of that ?
What 's this ?
You woke up Jair .
What 's this madness .
Leonardo , let 's go inside and I 'll explain .
Dad .
Coquito .
Santino , go inside , it 's cold .
Yes , let 's go inside .
Do something , take him away .
Coquito , prepare a bag with clothes , toys ,
and something warm , we 'll hit the road .
What ? Santino isn 't going anywhere .
You are the one leaving .
We all will leave .
There 's a rotten in the town .
A possessed one , Sabrina .
I think it is free .
This town will turn into hell quickly .
Shall I call the lawyer ?
Call the police , take him away .
He 's scaring the kids .
Dad , can Roger come with us ?
Yes , go prepare a bag , hurry up .
Make him leave , please .
I 'm hitting the road .
He 's scaring the kids .
Dad , can Vicky come ?
Yes , we will all go , go wake up your brother .
Vicky isn 't going anywhere , Santino neither ,
you are leaving .
I 'll call the police .
I made the decision , I 'm sorry .
Santino ,
wake up your brother , we are leaving now .
What can 't you understand ?
I make the decisions here .
They aren 't going anywhere .
Have you heard me ?
You are scaring my family .
A fucking rotten in the town .
Fuck you two .
I saw him , I was with him .
We have to leave , all of us .
- Where are the car keys ? - What keys , you idiot !
I don 't want to argue .
Stop , where are they ?
You are lying .
You are just lying .
Why are you screwing me ?
Can 't you see me happy ?
You come here to make me feel bad ,
scaring the kids .
Fucking crazy .
You disappeared for four years , not a single dollar ,
and now you come back .
I let you see the kids like a fool , and what for ?
You come and screw with my life .
Crazy fool .
What have I done to deserve this ?
Leave .
Start a new life , loser .
I don 't want you here .
Stop yelling .
Stop yelling !
Leave , you hear ?
There 's a restraining order , come to your senses .
What can I do to make you understand ?
You must understand ,
I 'm telling you there 's a rotten ,
how can 't you understand ?
You are insane .
Are you conscious of your words ?
Mom ! Dad ! Leo !
I saw him myself . How must I tell you ?
What 's up ?
Roger bit Vicky , it 's hurting her .
No !
No ! Vicky !
Get him ! Get him !
No !
No , no .
Vicky !
Roger !
Get him !
Leo !
My daughter , where is she ? Help me .
Help me , where is she .
Where is she ?
Pedro , what happened ? Where is she ?
Where is my daughter ?
Santino , son .
Santino , we 'll leave , stay here , yes ?
Jair , son , it 's dad .
Son , son , look at me .
It 's dad , it 's dad .
Listen .
No , don 't bite yourself , calm down .
Jair , son .
Son , look at me .
Look at me , look at me .
It 's dad .
Jair .
Don 't bite yourself , don 't do it .
Jair , it 's dad , I 'm here .
It 's dad .
Calm down , Jair .
Calm down .
Calm down , Jair , calm down .
Santi !
We are leaving ,
hurry up , son .
Where is she ?
Call the police .
Where 's the girl ?
Calm down .
Leo , don 't use guns .
Help me find my daughter , fucker .
Don 't use gun powder , Leo .
It 's your children 's sister , asshole .
Help me find her .
You won 't find a dog ,
you 'll find a demon .
Leo .
Leo , drop the gun .
Don 't use the gun .
Leo .
Damn it .
Yazurlo , what 's going on now ?
A dog .
It attacked my ex 's daughter .
A big , brown dog .
You called for a dog ?
It took her , Gutierrez .
It took her .
Call base .
What happens , Yazurlo ? What 's up ?
Another mistake ?
I 'm talking to you .
You heard me .
You can 't be here .
You know you can 't get close to your wife .
I 'm talking to you , what have you done ?
Don 't shoot the dog , don 't do it .
You are ok , love .
Thanks , where is Leo ?
Tell him she is ok .
Tell him .
You are ok , love .
Vicky is back , she is back .
Love , look at me .
Does it hurt ?
Where is Leo ?
Tell Leo Vicky is fine , please .
Are you ok ?
Look at me .
Does it hurt ?
Go tell Leo , please .
Vicky is fine , tell him .
The car keys .
Where are they ?
Son , Jair , it 's me , it 's dad .
Listen , where are the keys of mom 's car ?
Do you know ?
- Go fetch Jair 's bag . - He doesn 't have one .
- What then ? - A drawing .
Bring it , where is it ?
- Where is it ? - He is holding it .
Do you want ice-cream ?
Let 's go have ice-cream .
Apple ice-cream ? Let 's have one .
I can 't find the car keys .
I can 't .
I 'll go .
I 'll go , Santi , I 'll get the car .
When I find the keys of the grey car in the garage ...
Dad will kill you .
What are you saying ?
Dad
will come home
in the car
and pum !
Love .
Dad , what happened ?
Dad , what was that noise ?
Leo , Leo .
Are you ok ?
Leo .
Call the ambulance , he is hurt .
It 's ok , easy .
What 's this surprise ?
I can 't believe it , they gave you the kids .
What happened ?
What a nice surprise .
- I don 't know ...
Sabrina ?
I Don 't know
Pedro , so nice .
Don 't they have school ?
Isn 't this Sabrina 's car ?
What have you agreed with her ?
Have you talked with Jimmy ?
No , I didn 't tell her .
What happened ?
Did someone die ?
Nobody died , don 't ?
We aren 't going to a wake .
We are too far away for that to happen .
That things happen in the cities .
You saw anything you didn 't understand ,
got scared
and manipulated .
It 's happening , mom .
Grandma , what 's a possessed one ?
I see you are sure , but you may be wrong .
We are sure .
- Grandma . - Stop , Santino .
Are you sure , too ?
Yes , Jimmy too .
Possessed , possessed .
- Grandma . - Stop , Santino .
What did you agree with Sabrina ?
What did she say ?
We are leaving town .
Sabrina knows , doesn 't she ?
Have you ever witnessed this ?
What ?
Do you know someone who saw a possessed one ?
No , never .
I don 't , except from you two .
You are making a fuss .
Grandma , what 's a possessed one ?
Something really , really bad .
It goes into a person
and uses it 's body to be born .
Like a disease ?
There 's a song , do you know it ?
No .
It 's famous .
They get into your body ,
they infect your mind ,
they take the most valuable thing in your life ,
your body is no longer your body .
That 's really bad .
Well ,
it 's not that bad if you take precautions .
Look , there are seven rules to follow
and remember when there 's a possessed one .
For what ?
So they don 't get into your head
and make you do stuff
you don 't want to do .
Don 't use electric lights .
Don 't stay close to animals .
Don 't have to take anything that was close to them .
Don 't hurt them .
And a very important rule ,
never , ever name the evil by its name .
Evil has a name ?
Of course .
Look ...
- Lucifer ... - Mom .
- Azrael ... - Mom .
Beelzebub .
You are naming them .
Yes , you are right .
There 's a very important rule , too .
Don 't shoot them with fire arms .
Stop , mom . Stop .
What else .
That 's it .
There 's one missing .
- Haven 't I told the seven ? - No .
That should be a rule .
Don 't forget the rules .
Azrael .
A simple apple ice-cream .
They don 't have apple .
This is not enough , though . Do you have money ?
It 's all I had with me .
Check .
I 'm telling you , I don 't have .
You didn 't ask me to .
I thought you were paying .
Dad .
I want to go home .
We need to get more money .
Dad .
How are we going to eat ?
I want to go home .
What about Jair ?
Where is a fucking apple ice-cream ...
Jair won 't stop .
Well , we can go back to town , we buy the ice-cream .
Mom , no .
How long could it take ?
No , mom , we can 't go back .
What are you doing with the phone .
- I told you to leave everything . - I didn 't .
No , it 's mine .
It 's mine .
It 's Sabrina .
Talk to your mother .
Dad , I want to talk to mom .
It can 't be her .
Dad , I want to talk .
Santino , it 's not mom .
Shall I answer ?
I want to talk to mom .
Hello .
You took my children .
I want them back .
The kids are alright .
Jair can 't be far from home .
He has to take his medicine , bring him back !
Jair will decompensate !
The kids are fine , Jair is fine , they are fine with me .
Realize your sons don 't love you .
They can 't see you .
They never want to go to your house ,
they don 't want to live with you .
Don 't you get it ?
That 's why I cheated on you .
That 's why I fucked everyone .
Sabrina .
You are no one .
A little man , a little man .
You gave me a broken kid .
You wanted to get rid of him .
You are a bastard .
And a murderer .
Everyone knows it .
I know where you are .
I 'll come get my kids
and get them back .
You don 't know what I 'm capable of .
Sabrina , I saw you die .
I 'll get my kids , do you hear ?
I 'll get -
Brother , what happened ?
What happened ?
Sabrina is dead .
Her husband hit her with the truck , he killed her .
That wasn 't Sabrina .
What do you mean ?
What ? What happened ?
She is dead , Jimmy .
I saw her die , I saw her .
I 'm not even sure of what 's going on .
I 'm going crazy .
I 'm a coward .
I can 't handle my life , I 'm a coward .
I doubt this is the right thing .
I took the evil to her ,
I almost killed them all .
We should have left as soon as we knew .
I should have never come back to this town .
Easy , don 't say that .
I 'm proud of you .
Come on , brother ,
the kids are watching .
They will get scared .
Come on .
You didn 't see what I saw .
I know someone that may be of help .
She lives half-way to the city .
What will you say ?
I 'm not sure ,
but I think she lived something similar to this .
She can lend us money , too .
Jair won 't stop .
He won 't until I get him apple ice-cream I promised .
Brother , get your head together .
Get up .
Mom will get upset .
She is Mirta .
How are you , ma 'am ?
I have no electrical power ,
but there 's room for everyone , stay as long as you want .
No , we are going to the city .
Thank you , anyway .
Pedro , are you sure we 'll be better in the city ?
Will she give us money ?
Yes .
Let 's stop for a while .
We are tired .
Jair needs changing .
Mirta is ok with this .
It 's better for her , she is alone .
We can 't , Jimmy .
We are going to the city , don 't change the plan .
Besides ,
tell her that ...
we 'll give her the money back because we are good people .
That 's an issue ,
she has the money in the bank .
It 's there until Monday .
We can meet her there .
Jair needs changing .
Dad , Jair pooped .
He pooped .
The kid looks rotten .
He is autistic .
Yes , you told me .
You saw a real possessed one , right ?
Why do you ask ?
You told me . When you lived in the city .
You were close to one .
Did I ?
Long ago .
That you got used to living among them .
I don 't know why I said that .
I 'm good at getting secrets out .
What did you come here for ?
I think we saw a possessed one for real .
Where ?
In town ?
You got scared .
It seems so .
If you saw a possessed one , you wouldn 't say " I think " .
You wouldn 't doubt a bit .
I 'm not sure what we saw .
Babies who don 't cry ?
Shadows that move on their own ?
Animals doing stuff they 'll never do ?
I don 't know what we saw .
Maybe it was my brother 's imagination .
But maybe not .
Maybe it 's real and I can 't understand .
Is that the brother who plugged the heater outtake ?
That was a lie his wife told to keep the children .
He suffered a lot .
People from town are bored and like talking shit ,
after all , it 's free .
It 's ok , darling .
Well , well .
Yes ?
Close your little eyes ,
don 't open them ...
He won 't sleep .
Are you staying up another night ?
I 'd rather mom tucks Santino in and I 'll look after Jair .
He won 't leave the car .
Let 's take turns .
No .
So , this is the famous Mirta .
Mirta .
Why are you smiling ?
I 'm not .
It was long ago .
I was younger .
She was , too .
Of course .
You were always a lovebird .
Always a lovebird .
Every year you cried like a pig .
You said you missed the teachers .
I love you , brother .
I 'm here , son , I 'm here .
It 's dad .
I 'll take care of you .
Nothing will happen to you .
Sabrina ?
Is that you ?
I 'm happy you are here .
I 'm a bit drugged .
I took my sleeping pills .
I came for my children .
Because they need me .
I 'm taking my children
to a place where no one can harm them .
Mom , I 'm cold .
Pedro .
Something 's going on .
I can 't say what I saw ,
but it wasn 't her , I thought it was Sabrina ,
but I don 't know .
Calm down .
I can 't say ,
but there 's someone with Santino .
I 'm not sure .
Calm down , mom .
I came down to tell you ,
because I 'm afraid .
I 'm afraid .
I didn 't know what to do .
Calm down .
- I was too scared . - Calm down .
- I didn 't know what to do . - Easy .
I came for my children .
Because they need me .
I 'm taking my children
to a place where no one can harm them .
Dad .
No , no !
Son .
She jumped , that fucker .
She jumped with Santino .
She took him .
Fucker .
Where is he ?
Where ?
He has to be here .
Look over there .
Son !
Jair .
Son .
Jair , son .
It 's dad .
Son , son .
Son , open , open .
Jair .
Jair , son , are you ok ?
Are you ok ? It 's dad .
Jair is fine .
What 's this blood ?
- Where did it come from ? - I don 't know .
Go get some flashlights .
We need flashlights .
Jaime .
Santino .
Son .
Are there more flashlights ?
Something to light .
Jaime , there 's a demon .
It took my nephew .
It 's inside the kid .
No , he is like that .
No , Jaime .
He is like that .
Shut up , Jaime , listen to me .
Come over here and look at the kid .
Look at his feet and hands .
A demon got into his head and is trapped .
I saw this in autistic people .
They invade their bodies but can 't figure out their minds .
They can stay lost in that limbo for a long time
without untying the knot , and then they possess them .
The kid can be possessed , do you get it ?
Jimmy , I need you , the flashlight .
Go get your brother , we need to get inside .
I can 't leave him alone .
It took Santino , it must be near .
It is near , it is everywhere .
Listen to me ,
both of you .
You have no idea what you 're dealing with .
The song says so .
If you are afraid of falling into a hole ,
It will put a hole under you .
There 's people like us , whose thoughts It can 't control .
But It can manipulate us ,
because in here ,
I 'm sure that it is here ,
It was , some time ,
It was and it got information .
It 's the seventh rule , don 't be afraid of dying .
She wouldn 't be here
if you weren 't afraid she would take the kids .
You can 't go get your kid .
You must understand why .
Your fear of losing him helps the demon .
Evil knows more about your fears than you do .
Then I 'll go , I 'll get Santino .
I promise I 'll find him .
I 'll go , too ,
she must be near town .
No , we have to find the rotten .
Kill the man to stop the beast from being born .
The rotten is dead or this won 't be happening .
No , no .
This is what we call " the birth process " .
For now , It just freed its essence .
It may not be physically born ,
so we have to kill it , to abort it as soon as possible .
We know where he is .
We do know .
It 's near General Piran .
That 's far from town .
How are you so sure ?
We ...
moved the man and took him there .
You moved a rotten ?
Knowing he was possessed ?
You idiots .
Jaime .
The town lights .
They are off .
They cut the power , they activated the protocol .
Who knows what 's going on .
It 's dangerous to go back .
Don 't use lights .
Be careful .
My husband was a shepherd ,
we had a church .
We were frauds .
The first possessed one in Buenos Aires
appeared in our church .
At first , I thought it was an actor we hired ,
until he puked over all of us .
He puked up the rest of the family
he had eaten the previous night .
God is dead ,
and the times of churches ended quickly .
Then the cobras appeared ,
those monks who taught us there was a way
of killing them before they were born .
That 's what we did for twelve years .
We took responsibility for the damage we did to faith .
Ambushes started growing in number .
It 's no surprise they killed the cleaner .
That 's why everything turned ...
secretive .
We had to be too careful .
We were old for this .
You lose your reflexes .
One night , my husband ...
didn 't come back from a cleaning .
Then I left town .
From evil ,
you only escape leaving everything behind
and running away
to a place even you don 't know existed .
That 's what I did .
Such a coincidence , you here ,
in the middle of nowhere .
What if evil finally found me inside Jaime 's head ?
What if It infected the town just for me ?
Why didn 't It take you instead of my son ?
Because you are the one who is afraid .
We 'll have to continue on foot .
If he moved or was moved ,
it will be impossible to find him .
There .
He must be there .
RURAL SCHOOL
Evil likes children , and children like evil .
Jimmy .
You told me you loved me .
I 'm hungry .
And cold , grandma .
Can you prepare something hot to drink ?
Tea or something .
I don 't want to get sick .
Turn the lights off .
How do you know it 's not too late ?
Because what Evil eats first when born
is the sound of nature .
Birds and crickets are still chirping .
No more lights .
Don 't use electric stuff .
Where is it ?
Is it here ?
Are you hiding it here ?
Can you tell me where it is ?
We came to help you .
What happened ?
Didn 't ...
Didn 't you smell it ?
What ?
The breath of the kids .
They won 't help us .
But you said it was here .
Or they are hiding it .
Somewhere .
I 've never seen such a thing .
I don 't know if I can deal with this .
All those kids together .
Is he coming here ?
Kids protect the rotten .
This is crazy .
Don 't scare him .
Kid .
Are you going to school ?
Listen to me .
Do you know about someone ,
or maybe your friends do ,
about someone hurt ,
injured near here ?
Did you find someone sick
or injured near here ?
Yesterday or the day before .
I 'm talking to you ! Answer me !
I 'll go inside and make him talk .
No .
It 's not a good idea .
Is there any other idea ? Any good idea ?
I 'll make him talk no matter how , I don 't give a damn .
No .
We can 't make mistakes .
Not one , our lives are at stake .
Let me think .
We shouldn 't rush now .
We have to keep an eye on each other .
Are you looking for Uriel ?
Yes , yes .
He 's at teacher Cortez 's house .
Where is that ?
Don 't you know ?
No , I don 't .
Near the traffic circle .
Traffic circle , yes .
An entrance with trees .
On the traffic circle ?
Can you come with us ?
Let 's go .
Mirta , come on .
It may not be like that ,
and there 's someone waiting for us .
A trap ?
We have no time , we have to find out .
Let 's go .
It 's a lie .
A lie , don 't go where he said .
He is not there , Uriel is in my house ,
in my house , in my house .
My father wanted to help and cure him .
I live there , in the hill , but please be careful .
Motherfuckers , stop lying , fuckers .
Motherfuckers .
They took my son , I want my son , fuckers .
Fuckers .
It is here , Pedro .
It is here .
If they send us somewhere else ,
it 's because they have him here .
Dead ...
the adults .
I have never seen this .
Did the kids do it ?
Those aren 't kids anymore .
Go get my stuff .
Don 't run .
Don 't hurry .
It 's possible It is down there .
I told you not to run .
Be careful .
We found you , motherfucker .
We found you .
You have to leave , he wants to kill you .
He wants to kill you , don 't you see it ?
The parents and teachers are dead , they are there inside .
Don 't move .
Don 't even move .
They covered the bodies with lime to hide the smell ,
so they can 't be found .
Please , you have to leave .
They are bad , you will die ,
you have to leave .
You will die .
We have to take him out . Hurry .
We have no more time .
Go away , you still have time . Go away .
No , no , no .
Come on , Pedro .
Pedro , don 't waste more time .
No , please , no .
One is alive .
It doesn 't matter , take the rotten .
We have no time .
You 'll die , leave , please .
You 'll die , leave .
Hurry , we have to take him out now .
You 're gonna get infected .
It 's here .
Is it alive ?
I don 't know .
He is moving .
Kill me .
Kill me now .
Don 't think about it .
The only way to kill him is using this .
Take him out .
Get this over with
Hurry , Pedro .
His nape , I need to see his nape .
I can 't .
I can 't lift him .
This goes into his nape , I need to see it .
I can 't .
Come , help me .
No .
I can 't do it alone .
Keep her away .
I have to dismantle the stage .
Do it then .
You wanted to kill yourself ,
with your kids ,
you can do that to me .
Shut up , fucker .
Shut up , shut up .
There 's an axe in the director 's office ,
the axe for the fires .
No , she is lying .
In a red cabinet .
She is lying .
I saw it .
Pedro ,
all of this is your fault .
Don 't listen , don 't let him manipulate you ,
take the rotten .
Do it for Santino ,
don 't let him die .
You can still save him .
Yes , yes , bring the axe .
No , Pedro .
Kill me .
It 's a trap , don 't leave me alone .
Don 't leave me alone .
No .
Fuckers .
No , no , no !
Pedro ...
There was ...
a voice in my head ,
which forced me to kill the person
who was going to help Uriel .
I cut his body into pieces ,
I fed it to the pigs .
I also ate , I ate from that body .
And your mom ?
What happened to her ?
The same that happened to your mother .
Slowly , son .
Breathe .
Come on .
Don 't bite .
Open .